

ANISH CHANDRA

GIS SPECIALIST, DEVELOPER IMAGE PROCESSING EXPART

Contact



Debagram,Nadia,West Bengal,India,741137



+919563257518



https://chandraanish100.github.io/Anishportfolio.github.lo/



chandraanish100@gmail.com

ঞ্চি Skills

ArcGis, ArcGIS Pro. (Image Processing)

•••••

000000

Autocad

Python(Data Science) HTML CSS

About Me

As a GIS Specialist I handle various types of GIS data like utility Network, Urban planning, Municipality landbase taxation etc.And i do many types of spatial analysis and Graphical presentation using Excel and various software.

My main aim I want to grow my future as a GIS Developer and that's why I focus on some language like Python,SQL,HTML,CSS And JavaScript.I already use this in Google Earth Engine and Arcgis, ArcGIS pro.

Education

M.Sc in Remote Sensing And GIS

2020-2022

JIS UNIVERSITY

B.Sc in Mathematics

2014-2018

KALYANI UNIVERSITY

Work Experience

VADSP Infotech Pvt Ltd January 2024- Present Sr Image Processing Expert

- · I work as an image processing expert.
- I Work in Drone data, Microwave Data, Sentinel, Landsat, and Others.
- I work in ArcGIS, ArcGIS Pro, Erdas Imagine, Q-Gis, eCognition, And Others

Map My India August 2023-November 2023 Sr GIS Specialist

- I work in NPCI Govt Project.Here I use ArcGIS, AutoCAD and Mapinfo.
- I learn small things in this company I use
 Photoshop and do some graphic work also but
 there in Delhi i face serious health issues that's
 why I not stay there.

Neogeo Technologies Pvt Ltd July 2022-August 2023 Jr GIS Engineer

- I Work in Lucknow landbase taxation management Project.
- Here I use ArcGIS, Excel and ArcGIS pro for Spatial analysis Geocoding QC QA Measurement Landbase and Calculation Tax .

Aerospace Private limited November 2021-April 2022 Internship in GIS Digitizer

(Cartographer)

- I work in Urban planning USA Project.
- Here I use ArcGIS and Qgis for digitise electricity crod line, Building footprint and various types of items.